大家好  我是谢尔顿博士
Hello, I am Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
欢迎收看由谢尔顿·库珀出品的《有趣的旗帜》
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun with Flags.
节目开始前  我想先公布
Before we get started, I'd like to announce
设计旗帜比赛的赢家
the winner of our design your own flag competition.
可惜没有
But I can't.
唯一的参赛作品来自网友"爱咪福乐75"
The only entry was from GameyGamer75,
我知道你上传的是自己屁股照片
and I know that was a jpeg of your buttocks.
本周这集十分特别
Now this week we have a very special episode
我们将介绍
where we explore the flags
热门影集《星际迷航》中的旗帜
of the popular entertainment franchise, Star Trek.
我很荣幸请到这位来帮忙的特邀嘉宾
And to help me, I'm pleased to introduce
网络名人
Internet personality,
《星际迷航:  下一代》剧中演员
former star of Star Trek: The Next Generation,
并且是我认识的唯一一位有幸被按比例
and the only guy I know lucky enough to be immortalized
做成小人偶的朋友
in 1/16 scale--
将激光枪设至欢乐档
set phasers to "Fun"...
改编自《星际迷航》中的句子
"set phasers to stun"[将激光枪设至击晕档]
欢迎我的好友  威尔·惠顿
...for my friend, Wil Wheaton.
谢尔顿  感谢你的邀请
Hi, Sheldon. Thanks for having me.
-很高兴能上贵节目  -停
- I'm happy to be here. - Cut.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
谢尔顿  你的表现如往常一样精彩
Sorry, Sheldon, you were brilliant as always.
威尔  你有点太呆板了
Wil, that was a little wooden.
呆板吗
Wooden?
别担心  也没那么烂
Don't worry, it wasn't terrible.
但这次可以像正常人一样说话吗
Just, this time, try to say it the way people sound.
开拍
And action.
我的好友威尔·惠顿
My friend, Wil Wheaton.
谢尔顿  感谢你的邀请
Hi, Sheldon. Thanks for having me.
我很兴奋能上贵节目呢
I'm excited to be here.
威尔  你将从哪一面旗帜开始介绍呢
So, Wil, what do you have for us first?
这面旗非常有意思
Well, this is an exciting one.
这是星际联邦的旗帜
This is the flag of the United Federation of Planets.
-这面旗有趣的地方在于...  -停
- Now what's interesting about this flag... - Cut.
又怎么了
What was wrong with that?
这节目叫"有趣"的旗帜
It's called "Fun with Flags."
不是有人死了在降半旗哀悼
They're not at half-mast, nobody died.
欢乐喜庆点好不好
Let's try and keep it upbeat.
我无意冒犯
Um, no offense,
但我从小就开始演戏
but I've been acting since I was a kid.
上个网络节目
I think I can handle a Web show
我应该不需要人家教
without a lot of direction.
此话不假
It's true.
在1982年  威尔就替卡通电影
In 1982, Wil played the voice
《勇敢鼠妈妈》里的一角配音了
of Martin the mouse in The Secret of NIMH.
你感动了我
You moved me.
原谅我的吹毛求疵
You'll have to forgive me.
我第一次当导演  只想尽善尽美
This is my first time directing, I just want it to be good.
-我也是  -很好
- So do I. - Great.
那这次就请你
So, this time let's try
像个真男孩  而非小木偶
more real boy, less Pinocchio.
开拍
And action.
停
And cut.
你知道我是无偿友情客串的吧
You realize that I'm doing this for free, right?
但目前为止  无偿都有点不值回票价呢
Yes. And so far, we're still not getting our money's worth.
再来一次
Let's try it again.
大家开开心心
Everybody's having fun.
开拍
And action.
威尔
So, Wil...
你要先介绍哪面旗帜呢
...what do you have for us first?
这面旗十分有意思哦
Well, this is an exciting one.
这面旗
This is the flag
可是星际联邦的旗帜
of the United Federation of Planets.
停
Cut.
有问题吗  "新手"导演
Problem, first-time director?
我是没发现啦
Oh, none that I could see.
我只觉得你跟我一样热爱旗子
I saw a man who loved flags almost as much as I do.
都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I got goose bumps.
他故意夸张演出
He was overacting on purpose.
真的吗
Really?
让我想起电影里寇克船长小时候呢
He reminded me of a young William Shatner.
谢尔顿  我很乐意上你节目
Listen, Sheldon, I'm really happy to do this for you,
但她要在这当找茬精的话  那就算了吧
but not if she's gonna be a huge pain in the ass the whole time.
他这么说我  你居然没意见吗
You gonna let him speak to me like that?
这个嘛...
Well...
你是我女朋友
you're my girlfriend
我不想你不高兴
and I don't want you to be upset.
但威尔·惠顿也是我朋友
Then again, Wil Wheaton's my friend
我也不想他不高兴
and I don't want him to be upset.
真是进退两难啊
This is a sticky wicket.
你有什么看法
What do you think?
我们去一边谈谈
Can I speak to you for a second?
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
欢迎你"自娱自乐"
Feel free to play with yourself.
我不管他是不是你朋友
I don't care for your friend,
他对我出言不逊
he's being rude to me.
你得叫他滚蛋
You need to ask him to leave.
艾米  你怎么能叫他滚蛋呢
Amy, I can't just ask Wil Wheaton to leave.
他好歹也是个二线明星
He's a minor celebrity.
只需费点唇舌解释  人们还是能认出他的
Once you explain who he is, many people recognize him.
行  那我走可以了吧
Fine. Then maybe I should go.
真的吗  那问题就能迎刃而解了
Could you? That would solve everything.
你最好了
You are the best.
今晚晚餐见吗
I'll see you at dinner tonight?
你不会想跟你的好友威尔
You sure you wouldn't rather have dinner
一起共进晚餐吗
with your friend Wil Wheaton?
细想一下  我还真想呢
Come to think of it, I would!
小妞你今天棒呆啦
You, little lady, are on fire.
每次来吃晚饭
Every time we eat dinner here,
你妈妈都不让我帮忙洗碗
your mother refuses to let me help with the dishes.
别往心里去  她想自己洗碗
Don't take it personally. She likes doing them by herself
单纯是怕被别人看她偷舔碗盘
so she can lick the plates with no one looking.
准备好要回去了吗
You ready to go?
行  我拿几件洗好的高领衣就走
Yeah, let me just grab a couple of fresh turtlenecks.
咱们家那么多地方  干嘛还要把东西
I don't understand why you keep your stuff here
统统都留在这里啊
when there's plenty of room at home.
哪有这回事
What are you talking about?
我就留了几件外套
All I have here is a few sweaters,
书  银行东西  电脑
books, bank stuff, computers,
信件  收藏品  药物跟电动除毛机
mail, collectibles, medicine and my electric body groomer.
我的格子纹小围脖
Ooh, there's my plaid dickie.
我在二手店花五毛钱买到的呢
Oh, got this at the Goodwill store for 50 cents.
不敢相信吧
Can you believe it?
感觉就值这个价呀
50 cents sounds right.
走吧
Let's go.
有点晚了呢
You know, it's kinda late.
何不干脆在这里过夜
Why don't we just spend the night here?
因为我们不住在这里啊
Because we don't live here.
我知道
I know.
你真知道吗  你自己说
Do you? You said when you got back from space
从太空回来后就搬进我公寓
you were gonna move into my apartment,
但半数时间我们都住这里
but half the time we stay here.
才没有呢
That's not true.
霍华德  我要洗衣服了
Howard, I'm doing laundry!
有什么需要我帮你洗的吗
You want me to put anything in for you?!
篮子里有我的内裤  拿去洗吧
There's some underwear in the hamper!
非常好  我刚好要试试新去渍棒
Oh, good! I got that new stain stick to try out!
谢谢你做我"两周前"要求的事啊
Thank you! I only put it on the list two weeks ago!
好吧  我懂你意思了
Okay, I see what you're getting at.
要不这周末吧
How about this weekend
我把所有东西都打包搬回咱家
I'll box up all my things and move them to our place.
谢谢
Thank you.
这两把光剑放在我们客厅肯定很帅
The lightsabers are gonna look great in the living room.
放衣柜里也不错  到时候决定吧
Or in the closet. We can decide later.
霍华德  帮帮忙
Howard, help!
我的手卡在食物垃圾处理机里了
My hand's stuck in the garbage disposal!
那你把手里抓着不放的食物放开啊
Let go of whatever piece of food you're holding!
你不是吧
Are you kidding?!
是一根完好无缺的好鸡腿呢
It's a perfectly good chicken leg!
某人像个大男孩一样  夜游晚归哦
Hey, look who's out after dark, like a big boy.
我跟威尔·惠顿去共进晚餐了
I was out raising heck with Mr. Wil Wheaton.
再让我们吃个四小时
Four hours more and we would have
就能吃垮"家乡"自助餐厅了
closed down the HomeTown Buffet.
-你不是跟艾米有约了吗  -是啊
- I thought you had plans with Amy. - Yeah, I did,
但威尔说艾米是找茬精
but then Wil called Amy a pain in the A-S-S.
她就不爽走人了
She got huffy and left,
然后我就跟威尔一起去吃晚饭了
then Wil and I headed out to dinner.
"家乡"自助餐厅  真的有家乡味呢
That place really did remind me of my hometown.
因为我家乡也有一家"家乡"自助餐厅
Because there we also have a HomeTown Buffet.
等等  威尔跟艾米吵架啦
Hold on. Wil and Amy had an argument?
对啊  挺剑拔弩张的
Yes, quite the kerfuffle.
然后艾米火大走人啦
Then Amy got mad and left?
夺门而出  一去不返
Walked right out the door.
然后你...
And you...?
跟威尔开心地吃了顿好价钱的晚饭
Enjoyed a delightful dinner at a reasonable price.
餐厅经理认出了威尔
The manager recognized Wil
同意让我们坐在冰酸奶机旁呢
and let us sit right next to the frozen yogurt machine.
正旁边哦
Right next to it!
比我现在跟你的距离还近呢
I was closer to it than I am to you right now.
兄弟  艾米可能在不高兴哦
Buddy, I think Amy might be upset.
为啥啊
Why's that?
你的朋友对她出言不逊
Because your friend was rude to her,
你还跟他一起去吃晚饭
and then you went to dinner with him.
这不就是我刚才说的而已吗
You're just repeating what I said.
你这只乳糖不耐症的学舌鹦鹉
It's like living with a lactose-intolerant parrot.
听我的  打给她吧
Trust me, call her.
行  你没跟我们一起吃晚餐  真可惜
Fine. It's a shame you didn't go to dinner with us,
因为你等下就只能尝到
because the buffet you're about to enjoy
屈辱的滋味了
only serves humble pie,
跟冰酸奶的味道完全不能比哦
a dessert much less tasty than frozen yogurt.
当时就坐这么近
I was this close.
有何贵干
What?
跟你说个笑话
You'll appreciate this.
莱纳德脑子抽风  说你在气我
Leonard has some ridiculous notion that you're mad at me.
告诉他没这回事
Tell him you're not mad at me.
说吧  给他个痛快
Go ahead, set him straight.
我是气你啊  谢尔顿
I'm mad at you, Sheldon.
吃根巧克力棒吧
Eat one of your Luna bars.
女人常以为自己在愤怒
Very often when women think they're angry,
其实只是肚子饿而已啦
they're really just hungry.
我不饿
I'm not hungry.
你朋友羞辱我  你也不干嘛
Your friend insulted me, and you didn't do anything.
对啊  我什么都没干啊
Precisely, I didn't do anything.
某人是不是该仔细想想自己在说啥啊
Now does someone feel like checking her emotional math?
继续吧兄弟  我看好你哦
Keep going, buddy, you're doing great.
谢尔顿  我是你女朋友
Sheldon, I'm your girlfriend,
你应该帮我的才对啊
and you should have taken my side.
就这样吧  我说完了  晚安
That's it. End of story. Good night.
哎哟  艾米在生气  莱纳德说得对
Wow, Amy's mad and Leonard was right.
今天真不可思议
What a weird day.
抱歉  让你们等这么久
Hey. Sorry this took so long.
你以前也在这打工过  你懂得
But you used to work here, you know how it is.
厨房又出事了吗
Kitchen slammed again?
是我只是个烂服务生  忘了吗
No, I'm a terrible waitress, remember?
你明天要搬家
So, is there anything I can do
我有什么能帮你的吗
to help you with the move tomorrow?
正好你提到此事
Now that you mention it,
我觉得明天不是一个搬家的好日子
I was thinking tomorrow might not be great.
-你又有什么借口了  -没借口
- What's your excuse this time? - No excuse.
只是呢  我是犹太人嘛  严格来说
It's just, you know, I'm Jewish, and technically,
安息日的时候我们得休息  不适合搬家
we're not supposed to drive or carry anything on the Sabbath.
怪神别怪我啊
So this one's on God.
要想赖神跟习俗可以
That might be a little more convincing
但你满嘴猪肉起司汉堡  谁信啊[犹太人不吃猪肉]
if you didn't have a mouthful of bacon cheeseburger.
我不是一个忠实信徒嘛
My religion's kinda loosey-goosey.
简单来说  只要乖乖牺牲包皮[割礼]
Basically, as long as you got your schmekel clipped
不戴十字架也没事啦
and don't wear a cross, you're good.
华仔  你答应过我会搬家的
Howie, you promised you'd move.
我会啊
And I will.
-谁信啊  -我真的会搬
- Yeah, right. - I will.
我怎么可能会一辈子都赖在
I'm obviously not going to live in my mother's house
我妈的家里不走呢  又不是小孩
for the rest of my life. I'm not a child.
我见过她帮你拍嗝
I've seen her burp you.
她不是帮我拍饱嗝
She did not burp me.
只是她拍我的背  我刚好打了个嗝
She was patting me on the back, and I happened to burp.
你不用去招待其他客人吗
Don't you have other tables you should be waiting on?
要啊  但我也说了  我是个烂服务员
Yeah, but I told you, I'm not good at my job.
伯纳黛特  相信我
Bernadette, listen to me.
他死也不会搬走
He is never gonna leave.
我开始觉得你是对的
I'm starting to think you're right.
好吧  我受够了
All right, I've had enough of this.
我是个成年人  我有成功的事业
I'm a grown man, I have a successful career.
看在上帝的份上  我还去过太空呢
For the love of God, I've been to space!
当我准备好时  我就会搬出去住
I will move out when I'm ready,
我不需要任何人没完没了地烦我
and I don't need anyone badgering me into it!
哎哟  我先告辞了
Wow, excuse me.
那话只是冲她说的
That was just for her benefit.
我明天就搬  我爱你  别离开我
I'll move tomorrow. I love you. Don't leave me.
艾米
Amy.
愤怒的艾米
Angry Amy.
有何贵干
What?
我考虑了一下之前发生的事
I've been thinking about what happened,
我希望这个礼物
and I hope this gift
能让事态缓和点
will make things better.
《星际迷航》系列DVD
Star Trek DVDs?
我为何需要这个
Why would I want this?
首先  不客气
First of all, you're welcome.
再者  如果你不熟悉威尔·惠顿的作品
Furthermore, not being familiar with Wil Wheaton's body of work
你就不可能意识到
there was no way for you to know
你曾对这样的一位国家瑰宝出言不逊
you were being rude to a national treasure.
准备迎接130小时的"早知道就听你"的吧
Get ready for 130 hours of "I told you so."
好吧  由我来告诉你都演了些什么
Fine. I'll just tell you what happens.
第一集  《远点遭遇战》
Episode one, "Encounter at Farpoint."
缓缓驶入
Fade in.
新进取号踏上了搜寻戴纳伯四号星球
The new Enterprise heads out on its maiden voyage
居住的班迪人之处女航行
to contact the Bandi people of Deneb IV.
卫斯理·克拉希尔登场了  扮演者是我兄弟...
Enter Wesley Crusher, played by my buddy...
她要爱不释手了
She's hooked.
一个时代的终结啊
An end of an era.
唉  真希望这些墙能诉说衷肠
Boy, if these walls could talk.
那这些墙会说"为何他这么喜欢自摸"
They'd say, "Why does he touch himself so much?"
是啊
Yeah.
真不敢相信今后将不住这里了
I can't believe I'm not going to live here anymore.
这里一直都是我的卧室
This has always been my bedroom.
那里就是我妈以前测量我身高的地方
Right here is where my mom used to mark my height.
真的哎
Oh, yeah.
五年级时的身高
Fifth grade.
六年级时的身高
Sixth grade.
七年级时的身高
Seventh grade.
八年级时的身高
Eighth grade.
九年级时的身高
Ninth grade.
我还记得我五岁那年
I remember when I was five,
拿着我的万圣节糖果躲在这个桌子下面
hiding under this desk with all my Halloween candy.
吃了一些M&M花生糖豆
Had some Peanut M&M'S,
迎来了我第一次过敏性休克
went into my first anaphylactic shock
然后被送去医院
and had to be rushed to the hospital.
回到家后  吃花生士力架来欢庆康复
Came home, celebrated with a Snickers,
紧接着又迎来第二次过敏性休克
went into my second anaphylactic shock.
你什么时候发现对坚果过敏的
When did you figure out you were allergic to nuts?
大概在第三次吃杏仁巧克力时吧
Sometime around the third Almond Joy.
好吧
Okay.
要开始把这些东西搬上货车吗
You want to start loading this stuff into the truck?
好  搬吧
Yeah, I guess.
能帮我个忙吗
Hey, would you do me a favor?
你们先走
Go on ahead.
我只想在旧居里再独享这最后一刻
I just want one last moment alone in my old room.
我们才不要站在搬家货车边上等着
We're not standing outside by the U-Haul
你在这自摸爽完一发
while you fondle yourself.
好吧  一起走吧
Fine, let's go.
什么风把你吹来了
What brings you in?
佩妮  如果你不介意
Penny, if you wouldn't mind,
我想跟你谈谈女生
I'd like to have a conversation about girls.
我早预感到我们迟早会聊到的
I had a feeling we'd have a talk like this sooner or later.
你某个奇怪的地方终于长毛了吗
Are you finally getting fuzz in weird places?
佩妮  拜托
Penny, please,
我现在进退两难
I'm on the horns of a relationship dilemma.
同时声明  我到19岁那年
And for the record, I had a full pubis of hair
就已经长完了浓密的阴毛
by the time I was 19.
同时我也声明...
And for the record...
你打算喝点什么
So what are you drinking?
今天超不顺
Well, it's been a rough day.
我通常喝甘菊茶
I usually go chamomile tea,
但我觉得喝那个没用了
but I don't think that's going to cut it.
你可以来一杯长岛冰茶呀
You could have a Long Island Iced Tea.
那个能舒缓我的神经吗
Will that calm my nerves?
好几次把我舒缓到裤子都"没了"
It's calmed the pants off me a couple of times.
来一杯
Sold.
你那巫师得来的心脏让你陷入麻烦了吗
So, the heart you got from the wizard giving you trouble?
问题不在我这  佩妮
The trouble isn't with me, Penny,
而在你们女人身上
it's with your gender.
总有一天  科学家们会发现
Someday, scientists will discover
女性的第二条X染色体除了胡说
that second X chromosome contains nothing
和废话之外  其他一无所有
but nonsense and twaddle.
是啊  艾米告诉我发生了什么事
Yeah, Amy told me what happened.
听着  道歉就行
Look, just apologize.
它会融解她的废话
It'll warm her twaddle.
那顶多治标不治本
It's a band-aid at best.
核心问题在于艾米和威尔互相讨厌
The core problem is that Amy and Wil do not like each other.
这点很莫名其妙  因为他们都为我痴狂
Which is baffling because they're both crazy about me.
我也喜欢他们俩
And I like them,
这表明他们是聪明人  并且还喜欢
which indicates they're bright and interesting
或曾演过《星际迷航》
and/or were on Star Trek.
亲爱的  你不能逼别人互相喜欢
Honey, you can't make people like each other.
非也
Not true.
莱纳德让我喜欢你
Leonard made me like you.
不瞒你说  这事可不容易啊
And let me tell you, that was a hard row to hoe.
干杯吧  姐们
Cheers, pal.
好家伙  这可真是一杯无与伦比的饮品
Boy, that is a treat that's hard to beat.
快让疯帽先生来吧  我要开个茶话会
Get the Mad Hatter on the horn, I'm having a tea party.
你或许该慢慢喝
You might want to pace yourself.
我常喝茶啦
I drink tea all the time.
我懂我在干嘛
I think I know what I'm doing.
我没资格批评一位长齐阴毛的人啊
Far be it from me to criticize a man with a full pubis.
谢尔顿  问题不在威尔·惠顿这  好吗
Look, Sheldon, your problem is not Wil Wheaton, okay?
你的问题在于你对待艾米的方式
Your problem is the way you treated Amy.
我的问题是我的茶喝光了
My problem is I'm out of tea.
拜托  有人对你女友出言不逊
Come on, someone insulted your girlfriend
你却听之任之
and you just let him do it.
我还以为德州爷们会为女友挺身而出呢
I thought you Texas guys stood up for your womenfolk.
得了吧  佩妮
Penny, please,
我可比头脑简单的乡野村夫有教养
I think I've evolved beyond my simple rustic upbringing.
抱歉
Sorry.
不过话说回来
On the other hand,
那个卑鄙小人敢对我女人口出狂言
that low-down polecat done wronged my woman.
"长岛"的酒劲上来了  德州仔
Welcome to Long Island, Tex.
艾米不应该被这样对待
Amy deserves better.
我们买绅士什锦果仁时
You know, when we buy the Planter's deluxe mix,
她会帮我先吃光巴西坚果
she eats all the Brazil nuts
这样我就不用看到它们
so I don't have to look at them.
她是独一无二的圣人与松鼠结合体
She's a unique blend of saint and squirrel.
对  她是的
Yeah, that she is.
给你
Here you go.
我无情麻木又自我
I'm a callous egomaniac.
她会离开我的
She's gonna leave me.
她不会的
No, she won't.
对  她不会的  我这么棒的男人
No, she won't. I'm great.
好了  现在
Okay, I have now
我正式搬出了我母亲大人的家
officially moved out of my mother's house.
现在我生活中唯一会在浴室
You are now the only woman in my life
撞见的裸女就剩你啦
who I'll see naked in the bathroom.
我知道这不容易
I know this wasn't easy.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
我没事
Oh, I'm fine.
我只是担心我妈
It's just her I'm worried about.
她不会有事的
Aw, she'll be okay.
-她是成年人  -我知道
- She's a grown woman. - I know.
只是我爸离开后
It's just ever since my dad left,
我就觉得  我对她有责任
I've felt responsible for her.
这对一个孩子来说责任太重了
That's a lot for a kid to deal with.
她总是很伤心
She was just so sad all the time.
我是唯一可以令她开心起来的人
Yeah, I was the only person who could cheer her up.
我还有"本与杰瑞"牌冰淇淋
Well, me and Ben and Jerry.
她很幸运能有你的陪伴
She's lucky you were there.
因为她  我才学魔术的
You know, she's why I first got into magic.
我会表演给她看
I would do little shows for her,
挂上床单  好像幕布一样
hang up a bedsheet like it was a curtain,
戴上礼帽  穿上披风
put on a top hat and cape.
表演中
And part way through the act,
我会说我需要从观众中请一位志愿者
I would say I needed a volunteer from the audience
做我美丽的助手
to be my beautiful assistant
邀请她上台
and invite her up on stage.
我依然记得她当时笑的样子
I can still remember the way she'd smile.
在那短暂的几分钟里  她...
For a few minutes, she'd...
忘了自己有多孤单
forget how lonely she was.
见鬼  走吧
Aw, crap. Let's go.
去哪里
Where we going?
搬个箱子
Grab a box.
我们今晚睡你母亲家
We'll sleep at your mother's place tonight.
可我想住在这里
No, but I want to live here.
在你告诉我那个
Well, you should've thought of that
傻逼催泪魔术故事前就该想到这点了
before you told me the stupid magic trick story.
我们不能谈谈吗
Can't we talk about this?
我的老公决不允许伤他老娘的心
No husband of mine is gonna break his mother's heart!
威尔·惠顿
Wil Wheaton!
等等  敲了几下了
Wait, how many was that?
谢尔顿  什么事
Hey, Sheldon, what's up?
你真的想知道吗
Wouldn't you like to know?
你喝酒了吗
Have you been drinking?
只是喝了茶
Just tea.
我这辈子喝过的最好喝的茶
The best tea I've ever had.
你来干嘛
Why are you here?
我告诉你吧
I'll tell you.
我是德州仔
I'm from Texas.
还需要我多说吗
Need I say more?
是的  多说一点我比较明白
Yeah, actually, a little more would be helpful.
你对我的女人出言不逊
You insulted my woman.
我是来为她讨回公道的
I'm here to defend her honor.
两下  敲了两下
Two! It was two.
威尔·惠顿
Wil Wheaton!
现在准备好接受制裁吧
Now prepare yourself for what may come.
谢尔顿  你不会真觉得我们会打起来吧
Oh, Sheldon, do you really think we're gonna fight?
我的拳头抬起来
My fists are not up here
可不是给巨型隐形奶牛挤奶的
because I'm milking a giant invisible cow.
是要把道歉的话从你嘴里揍出来的
They're up to beat an apology out of you.
好的  对不起
Okay, I'm sorry.
坐这么远的公车来可真不值啊
Well, that was a long bus ride for not very much.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你问的问题太多了  威尔·惠顿
You're asking a lot of questions, Wil Wheaton.
只是好奇问下
As a matter of idle curiosity,
你觉得你家哪片灌木丛
which of your shrubberies do you feel
可以被呕吐物施肥一下
would benefit from a thorough vomiting?
算了  我自己选
Never mind, I'll choose.
你在《伴我同行》里的表演太精彩了
You were so good in Stand by Me.
大家好  我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
欢迎收看谢尔顿·库珀出品的《有趣的旗帜》
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents: Fun with Flags.
这是非常特殊的一集
Get ready for a very special episode
我们将介绍
where we explore the flags
热门影集《星际迷航》中的旗帜
of the popular entertainment franchise, Star Trek.
我很荣幸请到这位来帮忙的特邀嘉宾
And to help us, I'm pleased to introduce a special guest--
出乎意料的  只需要给点油钱
surprisingly, it only took gas money
跟答应他有吃的就愿意来了
and the promise of free food to get him here--
勒瓦尔·伯特先生
Mr. LeVar Burton.
你好  谢尔顿  很荣幸来到这里
Hey, Sheldon, it's a pleasure to be here.
-有些很有意思的旗帜...  -停
- Well, we've got some interesting flags for... - Cut!
妈呀  这家伙比威尔·惠顿还烂
Yikes, this guy is worse than Wil Wheaton.
我不知道她在胡说什么
I don't know what she's talking about,
但我有义务同意她的话
but I'm obligated to agree with her.
她是我的女朋友
She's my girlfriend.
明白  兄弟
Ah, I hear you, brother.
我还是有免费午餐吃的  对吧
I still get lunch, right?